{"data":[{"question":"In the preparation of fibrous material for production uses, stiff woody fibers from plants ________ fibers from animal sources.","a":"the most heat the","b":"need more heat than","c":"than more heat needed","d":"need the more heat than","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Comparative of adj:\u00a0\n+ Short adj: Adj + er + than \n+ Long adj: More + adj + than \n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- S: stiff woody fibers from plants.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Partnership is an association of two or more individuals who ________ together to develop a business.","a":"worked","b":"they work","c":"work","d":"working","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Who (= individuals): is relative pronoun for subject.\u00a0\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Chosen as the nation's capital at the end of the American Civil War, ________ a city of over a million people.","a":"Washington, D.C., is now","b":"for Washington, D.C.,","c":"to Washington, D.C.,","d":"now in Washington, D.C.,","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- Use a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence to set off clauses, phrases, and words that are not essential to the meaning of the sentence.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Within an area of only 100 miles, Death Valley sinks to 282 feet below sea level while Mount Whitney ________ to a height of 14,494 feet.","a":"soaring","b":"soar","c":"soared","d":"soars","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mount Whitney is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The cosmopolitan flavor of San Francisco is enhanced by ________ shops and restaurants.","a":"an ethnic","b":"its many ethnic","c":"its ethnicity","d":"ethnicity","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adjective is used to modify noun and stands before noun.\u00a0\n- shops and restaurants is plural- \"an\" is not correct.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"________ that increasing numbers of compact-disc players will be bought by consumers in the years to come.","a":"They are anticipated","b":"In anticipation","c":"Anticipating","d":"It is anticipated","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Active: People\/ They + think\/ say\/ suppose\/ believe\/ consider\/ report ... + THAT + clause.\u00a0\n- Passive : IT'S + thought\/ said\/ supposed\/ believed\/ considered\/ reported ... + THAT + clause.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Birds all over the world ________ in distances up to thousands of miles.","a":"migrating","b":"migrated","c":"migrate","d":"are migrated","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Cellulose, which ________ for making paper, can be found in all plants.","a":"is used","b":"uses","c":"are used","d":"is using","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice: be + PP.\u00a0\n- Cellulose: is singular-is used.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"________, human beings have relatively constant body temperature.","a":"Alike all mammal","b":"Alike all mammals","c":"Like all mammals","d":"Like all mammal","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Alike is adverb or subject.\u00a0\n- Like: can be used as conjunction.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"So far there is no vaccine ________ in sight for the common cold.","a":"or curing","b":"has cured","c":"or cure","d":"having cured","answer":"3","explain":"\n -Parallel structure: structure before and after \"or\" must be parallel.\u00a0\nVaccine is noun- word after \"or\" must be noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}